Shubham Bangwal

Software Engineer

Gumaniwala Om Vihar Colony lane no.3, 249204 Rishikesh, India

💌 bangwalshubham34@gmail.com 📞 8126133883 🎬 04/03/1997 💄 Male 🔞 Unmarried

PROFILE

I'm a PHP Laravel programmer having 4 years of experience in building meaningful web applications and developed 6+ software like B2B, B2C, CMS, and Restful systems with the help of databases like MYSQL, PostgreSQL. Frontend Technologies As I have 4 years of experience in web development, due to that I gained good experience in Jquery/JavaScript and supporting in HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, UI, Accessibility, Angular, JS, etc. Third-Party Integrations... I have experience in many third-party API Integrations like Expedia, Google, Facebook, Stripe, Paytm, eBay, Firebase, SetaSign, Base64ai, etc... An extensive experience I have extensive experience with DevOps tools like GIT, FileZilla, BitBucket, SourceeTree, Jira, Slack,, etc.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

01/2020 - 10/2022 Noida, India

workrush Pvt Ltd

Web Developer

- Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript, AJAX, and JSON coding.
- Multi-tasked across multiple functions and roles to generate project results and meet deadlines and organizational expectations.
- Engaged with clients to plan, optimize and repair site issues.
- Built and styled new mobile-friendly websites, transitioning legacy presentations to simultaneous easy-to-use versions.
- Implemented REST API's for mobile applications.
- Conducted testing and review of website design for responsiveness, clarity, and effectiveness.
- Write, design, or edit web page content, or direct others producing content..

11/2022 - present Kolkata, India

Brainium Information Technologies Pvt Ltd 🗷

Software Developer

- · Work closely with clients to understand their business needs.
- Gather and document detailed specifications for software development projects.
- Clarify and validate client expectations to ensure a clear understanding of project goals.
- Provide updates on project progress, address concerns, and manage client expectations.
- Act as a bridge between the client and the development team, ensuring effective information flow.
- Collaborate with clients to define project timelines, milestones, and deliverables.
- · Create project plans and ensure that development activities align with client priorities.
- · Address and resolve issues or concerns raised by clients in a timely and efficient manner.
- Work with clients to define and execute test plans to ensure software meets quality standards.
- Explain technical concepts in a clear and understandable manner to client.

PROJECTS

Ebthree

https://ebthree.com/

EB3 is an online system used to automate the process of creating Fully Customizable Employee Benefit Booklets. Users (Agents, Agency or Enterprise) can create a Booklets within a minute according to company benefits information. EB3 provides mulitple Plans, Pages, Legal Notices and Compliances to users so, Insurance Company Agents can create thier own Insurance Booklets

Footbus

https://www.footbus.com/

The Footbus is an app to create, manage and share walking routes. Footbus makes meeting up and walking with friends easily and hassle-free.

Rifilesgym

https://riflesgym.co.uk/

The Rifles app is a gym class scheduling app.

The App has a unique monitoring system for personal progress monitoring and class schedule.

Live happy

It is a fitness application. live-happy gives you online classes for physical and mental wellbeing.

G10 Assists

G10 Assists provides buddy service to retired persons & elderly people who need assistance with daily household chores. All our buddies are verified and you get their complete background details when you avail of buddy service from G10 Assists.

Clean Medic

https://dev.cleanmedic.co.id/admin/login

Clean Medic provides a service in which they collect wastage from producer and store in their factory or warehouse and decompose the waste.

EDUCATION

2015 - 2019 Btech

Jollygrant, India Swami Rama Himalayan University

2014 **12th**

Rishikesh, India Shri Guru Ram Rai Public School

2012 **10th**

Rishikesh, India Shri Guru Ram Rai Public School

SKILLS			
PHP Laravel Framework	• • • •	REST API devlopement in laravel	••••
Django Framework	• • • • •	React	• • • • •
Angular JS	• • • • •	Ajax	• • • • •
jQuery	• • • • •	Nodejs	• • • • •
AWS EC2, S3, Create Instances, Project (● ● ● ● ● ● ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■	NextJs	• • • • •